Gross, James A. Arbitration Files 5697
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
James A. Gross Arbitration Files
1966-1986
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Gross, James
5697
16 cubic feet
16 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3122423
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 12, 1999
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 27, 2019
Scope and Contents
These arbitration files are coded to indicate what is included in the file: TR = Transcript(s) EX = Exhibit(s) AN = Arbitrator's Notes RC = Routine Correspondence A = Agreement SD = Supporting Document(s)
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4057: James A. Gross NLRB Files /4057 AV: James A. Gross NLRB Audiocassettes /4057 P: James A. Gross NLRB Photographs /4079: James A. Gross Additional Files /4124: James A. Gross Papers, Additional NLRB Research Files /4166: James A. Gross Additional NLRB Research Files /4186: James A. Gross Additional Research Files /4190: James A. Gross Additional Research Files /4285: James A. Gross Research Files Additional /4232: James A. Gross Collection of NLRB 60th Annual Conference Files 5959: James A. Gross Additional Arbitration Files
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States.; Gross, James A.
3122423
- Abbott Manor Nursing Home vs. New York State Nurses Association, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Issue: Union Representatives and Business--Dues. RC, A, LD, AN.
- Allied Chemical Company (Syracuse) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 12457, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Issue: Seniority--Transfers. RC, AN, A, EX, SD.
- Almeida Bus Lines vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 59, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Issue: Falsification--Company Records in General; Theft--Company Property. RC, SD, AN, EX.
- American Sugar Company vs. Sugar Refinery Workers, Local 1660, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Issue: Contracting Out. RC, TR, SD, EX. A, AN, LD.
- Borden, Inc., Foods Division, Can Manufacturing Plant at Lyons, NY vs. Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Section 482, FLM Joint Board, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Issue: Grievance and Grievance Procedure--Multiple Grievance Arbitrations. AN, RC, SD, A, EX.
- Boston, City of vs. Boston Police Collective Bargaining Federation, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Issue: Grievance and Grievance Procedure--Arbitrability. SD, A, EX, AN, RC, TR, LD.
- Boston, City of vs. Boston Police Collective Bargaining Federation, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Boston, City of vs. Boston Police Collective Bargaining Federation, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Bradford Central School District vs. Bradford Teachers Association, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Issue: Arbitrability--Timeliness; Termination of Employment--Failure to Qualify for Promotion (Tenure); Notice. NA, RC, SD, LD, EX, A, AN.
- Brewer-Titchener Corporation vs. UAW, Local 1774, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Issue: Discipline--Discharge; Falsification--Daily Time Record. RC, A, SD, AN, EX.
- Brewer-Titchener Corporation vs. UAW, Local 1774, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Issue: Seniority--Bumping. RC, A, SD, AN, EX.
- Brewer-Titchener Corporation vs. UAW, Local 1774, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Issue: Union Representatives and Business--Shift Transfers; Seniority--Eligibility. RC, EX, AN, SD.
- Buffalo Forge Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1974, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Issue: Discipline--Discharge; Fights and Altercations--Assault on Fellow Employee RC, EX, SD, AN.
- Carborundum Company vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, AFL-CIO, and Abrasive Workers Local 8-12058, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Issue: Discipline--Layoff As. EX, RC, AN, SD, LD.
- Cayuga County Community College vs. Cayuga County Community College Faculty Association, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Issue: Union Representatives and Business-- Leaves of Absence. RC, AN, EX, SD, LD.
- Crompton and Knowles Corporation, Worcester Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3274, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Issue: Improper Job Attitude-- Tardiness; Fights and Altercations--Assault on Supervisor. RC, A, SD, AN.
- Dresser Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1630, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Issue: Layoff--Recall; Recall--Failure To Report; Discipline--Late Lunch. RC, SD, AN, TR, EX.
- Dresser Industries, Incorporated, Clark Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4601, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Issue: Grievance And Grievance Procedure-- Filing Requirements. EX, AN, RC, SD, TR.
- Dresser Industries, Incorporated, Clark Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4601, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Dresser Industries, Incorporated, Clark Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4601, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Dresser Industries, Incorporated, Clark Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4601, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Dresser Industries, Incorporated, Clark Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4601, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Dresser Industries, Incorporated, Clark Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4601, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Issue: Union Security--Job Jurisdiction RC, AN, SD.
- Eastern Container Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, Local 284, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Issue: Absences--Excuses; Physical Disability--Recall. RC, LD, AN, SD, EX.
- Eaton Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, Local 78, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Issue: Seniority--Recall. EX, RC, AN.
- Eaton Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers, and Helpers, Local 78, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Issue: Testing of Employees--Ability; Union Security--Job Assignment.
- Elmira City School District vs. Custodial Maintenance and Cafeteria Employees, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Issue: Transfers--Reduction in Force; Management Rights. RC, LD, AN, EX.
- Erie, County of, Erie Community College vs. Faculty Federation of Erie Community College, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Issue: Classification of Jobs--Duties Performed. RC, AN, EX.
- FMC Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 1180, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Issue: Theft--Company Property; Intent. EX, RC, AN.
- First National Stores, Incorporated vs. Amalgamated Meat Cutters, Food Store and Allied Workers, Local 592, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Issue: Discipline--Demotion; Classification of Jobs--Elimination of Jobs; Employees Rights--Overtime; Union Security--Assignment of Jobs. RC, A, LD, AN.
- Golden Fleece Tissue Mills, Division of Standard Packaging Corporation vs. United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 659, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Issue: Layoff-- Recall; Seniority. RC, LD, A, SD, AN.
- Gould's Pumps, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3298, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs. EX, RC, AN, SD, A.
- Great Lakes Carbon Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 12896, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Issue: Discipline--Discharge; Absences--Excessive. EX, A, RC, AN, SD.
- Griffiss Air Force Base, Headquarters, 416th Combat Support Group, Department of the Air Force vs. American Federation of Government Employees, Local 2612, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Issue: Discipline--Violation of Plant Rules. RC, AN, EX, SD, A.
- Hercules, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 12962, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Issue: Improper Job Attitude--Verbal Disrespect. EX, A, RC, AN, LD.
- Hooker Chemical Corporation vs. Niagara Hooker Employees Union, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Issue: Absences--Excessive. RC, EX, A, AN.
- Hooker Chemical Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District 76, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Issue: Reduction In Force-- Assignment of Jobs. EX, A, AN.
- Hooker Chemical Corporation vs. International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers, Local 57, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Issue: Reporting Pay--Weather Conditions. EX, A, RC, SD, AN.
- Holbrook Drop Forge Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2936 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Issue: Fringe Benefits--Cost of Living Allowance. NA, RC, LD, EX, A, AN.
- ILCO Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, Local 290 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Issue: Discipline--Discharge; Alcoholism, Drinking, and Intoxication--Drinking on the Job. NA, EX, A, AN, LD, RC. Settled.
- Interspace Corporation vs. Federal Labor Union, Local 22485 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Issue: Insubordination--Failure to Obey Orders; Profanity. EX, A, RC, AN, SD.
- Ithaca, City of vs. Civil Service Employees Association, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Issue: Classification of Jobs--Evaluation of Job Factors. RC, EX, AN.
- Ithaca City School District vs. Ithaca Teachers Association, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Issue: Grievance and Grievance Procedure--Waiver; Contract Interpretation-- Inconsistent Provision. AN, RC, EX, A, SD.
- Keith Clark, Incorporated vs. International Typographical Union, Sidney Local 81, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Issue: Contract Interpretation--Layoff Procedures. EX, A, RC, AN, SD.
- Kennedy Valve Manufacturing Company, Incorporated vs. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 329, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Issue: Incentive Pay and Incentive Systems--Rate Revision. EX, A, RC, AN.
- Kennedy Valve Manufacturing Company, Incorporated vs. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 329, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Issue: Holidays and Holiday Pay--Refusal of Overtime. RC, AN, EX, A, SD.
- Kraft Foods vs. Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 34, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Issue: Rates of Pay--Error. RC, AN, LD, SD, EX, A.
- Kraft Foods vs. Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 34, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Issues: Contracts--Side Agreement. EX, AN, EX, A, LD.
- Lancaster Central School District vs. Lancaster Central Teachers Association, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Issue: Management Rights--Testing of Employees.
- Lipe-Rollway Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 14929, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Issue: Union Security--Assignment of Jobs.
- Lipe-Rollway Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 14929, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Issue: Management Rights--Time Studies. NA, A, EX, RC, AN.
- Loud-Wendell, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local Lodge 1180 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Issue: Discipline--Refusal of Overtime; Layoff--Recall. RC, AN, EX, A, SD.
- Lynn Hospital vs. Massachusetts Nurses Association, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Issue: Contract Modification. RC, TR, AN, EX, A, LD, SD.
- Lynn Hospital vs. Massachusetts Nurses Association, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Marcus Whitman Central School vs. Marcus Whitman Professional Association, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Issue: Contract Interpretation--Hours Worked. RC, AN, A, EX.
- Monroe, County of vs. Monroe County Chapter of Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1976 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Issue: Contracts--Effective Date. RC, AN, EX, A.
- Morse Chain Division of Borg-Warner Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 1607, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Issue: Classification of Jobs--Evaluation of Job Factors. AN, SD, EX, A.
- Morse Chain Division of Borg-Warner Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 1607, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Issue: Absences--Excessive. EX, A, RC, SD.
- Morton Salt Company vs. Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-625, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Issue: Layoff--Ability vs. Seniority. AN, EX, A, RC, SD.
- National Automobile Parts Association vs. United Auto Workers, Local 209, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Issue: Absences--Holiday Pay Eligibility. RC, SD, LD.
- Native Textiles vs. Communications Workers of America, Local 1127, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Issue: Arbitrability--Timeliness; Schedules of Work--Early Send-Home. RC, EX, A, AN, SD, LD.
- Nestle Company, The, Incorporated vs. United Food and Chocolate Workers Union, Local 1974, Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Issue: Layoff--Seniority. EX, A, AN, RC, SD.
- Nestle Company, The, Incorporated vs. United Food and Chocolate Workers Union, Local 1974, Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Issue: Improper Personal Conduct--Sleeping On The Job. AN, SD, EX, A.
- Newman-Crosby Steel Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, District 1, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Issue: Classification of Jobs--Discontinuance of Classification. NA, SD, RC, AN, EX, A, LD.
- New York Telephone Company vs. Communications Workers of America, District 1, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Issue: Discipline--Suspensions. NA, RC, EX, A, AN.
- Newton Falls Paper Mill, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 687, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Issue: Layoff. NA, RC, EX, A, LD, SD.
- Newton Falls Paper Mill, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 687, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- New York State Electric and Gas Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, System Council U-7, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  Issue: Falsification-- Delivery Records; Theft--Company Product
- Niagara, County of vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, Council 66, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  Issue: Bumping--Reduction in Force. RC, AN, EX, LD, A.
- Niagara-Wheatfield Central School District vs. Niagara-Wheatfield Teachers Association, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Issue: Classification of Jobs--Added Duties. EX, A, RC, SD, LD, AN.
- Northrop Corporation vs. UAW, Local 1596, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Issue: Layoff--Seniority, Failure To Observe--Overruled. RC, AN, EX, A, SD, TR.
- Northrop Corporation vs. UAW, Local 1596, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Owens-Illinois Company vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 170, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Issue: Holidays and Holiday Pay--Eligibility in General. LD, RC, EX, A, SD, AN.
- Perkins Machine and Gear Company vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, Local 268, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Issue: Holidays and Holiday Pay--Eligibility in General. EX, RC, LD, AN, SD, A.
- Phelps-Clifton Springs Central School vs. Phelps-Clifton Springs Faculty Association, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Failure To Assign. SD, RC, EX, A, AN.
- Rico Machine Company, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 7255, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Issue: Fights and Altercations--Assault on Supervisor; Verbal Assaults; Insubordination--Failure to Obey Orders. RC, SD, AN, EX, A.
- Rochester City School District vs. Rochester Teachers Association, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Issue: Contract Interpretation--Rates of Pay. RC, EX, A, AN.
- Rochester Telephone Corporation vs. Communications Workers of America, Local 1170, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Issue: Alcoholism, Drinking and Intoxication--Events Subsequent to Discharge. SD, RC, AN, EX, A, LD.
- Rochester Telephone Corporation vs. Communications Workers of America, Local 1170, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Issue: Alcoholism, Drinking and Intoxication--Events Subsequent To Discharge. RC, EX, A, SD, AN.
- Rome City School District vs. Rome Teachers Association, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  Issue: Leaves of Absence--Vacation Eligibility. NA, RC, LD.
- Rome City School District vs. Rome Teachers Association, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Issue: Compensation--Rates of Pay. RC, A, SD, LD, AN, EX.
- Schoeller Technical Papers, Incorporated vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Local 1066, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  Issue: ShutdownSeniority. RC, EX, A, AN, SD.
- Simplex Wire and Cable Company vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 2261, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  Issue: Discipline--Overtime. RC, AN, EX, A, SD.
- South Seneca Central School District vs. South Seneca Teachers Association, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  Issue: Contract Modification--Wage Adjustments. RC, AN, EX, A.
- Sperry Univac vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Greater Lodge 1063, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Issue: Classification of Jobs-- Combination of Classifications. EX, A, SD, AN, RC.
- Stop and Shop, Incorporated, Boston vs. Retail Store Employees Union, Local 826, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Issue: Insubordination--Refusal of Work Assignment. RC, LD, A, AN.
- Strong Memorial Hospital vs. 1199 National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Issue: Ability--Assignment of Jobs; Discrimination-- Assignment of Jobs. SD, EX, A, RC, AN.
- Susquehanna Valley Board of Education vs. Susquehanna Valley Teachers Association, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Added Duties. RC, AN, SD, EX, A.
- Susquehanna Valley Board of Education vs. Susquehanna Valley Teachers Association, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Change In Duties. NA, RC, AN, EX, A, SD, LD.
- Sweet Home Central School District Board of Education vs. Sweet Home Education Association, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  Issue: Fringe Benefits--Insurance and Medical Plans.
- Syracuse University vs. General Service Employees' International Union, Local 200, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Issue: Improper Personal Conduct--Abusive, Quarrelsome and Uncooperative. RC, A, AN.
- Thompson Steel Company, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3234 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Issue: Seniority--Bumping. A, EX, RC, AN, SD, LD.
- Utica City School District vs. Utica Teachers Association, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Issue: Termination of Employment--Failure To Qualify For A Promotion. LD, RC, SD, EX, AN.
- Victory Markets, Incorporated vs. Amalgamated Meat Cutters District Union, Local 1, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Issue: Improper Personal Conduct--Mode of Dress. EX, RC, AN, A, SD.
- Ward-LaFrance Truck Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 421, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Issue: Union Security-- Assignment of Jobs. RC, EX, A, AN, SD.
- Waverly Board of Education vs. Waverly Teachers Association, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Issue: Union Security--Contracting Out. RC, EX, A, AN, LD.
- West Canada Valley Central School District vs. West Canada Valley Teachers Association, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Issue: Arbitrability--Promotions; Termination of Employment--Failure To Qualify For Promotion.
- Westinghouse Broadcasting Company vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1228 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Issue: Improper Personal ConductAssaults. RC, AN.
- Wyman-Gordon Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, District 1, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Issue: Reporting Pay--Notice Not To Report. AN, RC, EX, A, SD.
- Wyman-Gordon Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, District 1, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  Issue: Classifications of Jobs--Change in Work Assignments. A, EX, RC, AN, SD.
- Albany State Police vs. The Police Benevolent Association of the New York State Troopers, Incorporated (Trooper Matthew C. Heeson), 1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Issue: Vacations --Illness During, Effect. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Albany Steel and Iron Supply Company, Incorporated vs. International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, Local 534, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Issue: Discipline--Discharge; Improper Job Attitude--Neglect of Duty. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Albany Steel and Iron Supply Company, Incorporated vs. International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, Local 534, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Albany Steel and Iron Supply Company, Incorporated vs. International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, Local 534, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Alco Power Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, Local No. 3482, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Issue: Overtime--Call-In For Overtime. EX, AN, RC, A.
- Allegheny International, Special Metals Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local Lodge No. 2310, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Issue: Discipline--Suspensions. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Allegheny Ludlum Industries, Incorporated, Special Metals Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local Lodge 2310 of District 157, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  Issue: Schedules of Work--Notice. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Allegheny Ludlum Industries, Incorporated, Special Metals Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local Lodge 2310 of District 157, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Allied Chemical Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local Union 12457, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  Issue: Alcoholism, Drinking, and Intoxication--Drinking Prior To Reporting; Evidence. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Allied Chemical Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local Union 12457, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Allied Chemical Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local Union 12457, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Allied Chemical Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local Union 12457, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- American LaFrance vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge No. 421, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  Issue: Vacations--Vacation Preference. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- American LaFrance vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge No. 421, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Amsterdam Printing and Litho Corporation vs. Graphic Arts International Union, Local 259, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  Issue: Arbitrability--Contract Violation. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Amsterdam Printing and Litho Corporation vs. Graphic Arts International Union, Local 259, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Amsterdam Printing and Litho Corporation vs. Graphic Arts International Union, Local 259, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Auburn Enlarged City School District vs. Anthony P. St. Phillips, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  Issue: Improper Personal Conduct (Section 3020-A of the Education Law, Tenure). NA, TR, AN, RC.
- Auburn Enlarged City School District vs. Anthony P. St. Phillips, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Auburn Memorial Hospital vs. New York State Nurses Association, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  Issue: Rates of Pay--Increase. EX, AN, RC, A.
- Auburn Memorial Hospital vs. New York State Nurses Association, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Auburn Memorial Hospital vs. New York State Nurses Association, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Binghamton City School District vs. Binghamton Teachers Association, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Employee Preference. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Binghamton City School District vs. Binghamton Teachers Association, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Binghamton City School District vs. Binghamton Teachers Association, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Binghamton City School District vs. Binghamton Teachers Association, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Boise Cascade Corporation Latex Fiber Products vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Local No. 1799, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  Issue: Holidays and Holiday Pay--Leaves of Absence EX, AN, RC, A, SD.
- Boise Cascade Corporation Latex Fiber Products vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Local No. 1799, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Borden Chemical, Division of Borden, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Bainbridge Lodge No. 1278, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  Issue: Posting. EX, AN, RC, A, SD.